

### **PROFILE**

Full Stack Developer with over 4.9 yrs of experience. Skilled Java with ReactJs using GIT and Javascript with Agile development methodology. I consider myself a responsible and orderly person. I looking forward better opportunity in Senior Developer with DevOps Skills. I always look for change to gain different experiences in my industry.

## **EDUCATION**

**GGSIPU JUL 2016- MAY 2019** B.Voc(Software Development)

**IGNOU 2022-24**MCA- waiting for Degree

# SAADHYA

React/Frontend Developer
Dob: 25-03-1998



# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Consultant at Capgemini Engineering (15th April 2024-Present)

Working as Frontend Developer with ReactJs and Redux for the Production Management Project of American Publicly Traded company.

Using Visual Studio, Swagger & .Net as well.

Full Stack Developer at AVPS
Technologies
(5th Aug 2019-12th April 2024)

## PROJECTS AT AVPS TECHNOLOGIES

#### INTERVIEW APP - 1 YEAR

Its kind of quiz webapp developed on React with Java backend for my own company for hiring new employees.

I was the only frontend developer on the project. I built the whole application in React and integrated the app with Java.

### **CONTACT ME**



+91 9599619705



saadhya98@gmail.com



B-257/10, Ashok Nagar, Shahdara, Delhi-110093, INDIA

https://github.com /Saadhya

https://www.linked in.com/in/saadhya9

https://saadhya.git hub.io/

# **SKILLS**

- Expertise in responsive frontend component design-HTML5, CSS/SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Material-UI, Redux. ReactJs, thunk, Tailwind, webpack and babel.
- Tools- GIT, VS Code, JIRA, Invision App, gitbash, JSF, Gitlab, Rest APIs, SpringBoot, Node, Java,
- AWS DynamoDb, CodePipeline, SQL server, MongoDb, Bootstrap
- Excellent Troubleshooting and Project Management Skills.
- API Integration with Restful Services into Frontend components

# **ELECTRIC VEHICLE INDUSTRY-6MONTHS**

I developed the dashboard for this client on React. I mostly worked on frontend designs and integration part. This includes managing customer, charging stations in LA with onspot payment, payments wallet etc.

## AVPS ACADEMY - (1.5YEAR)

Developed Educational webapp to manage students with their attendance on live course, tutors and their courses, small quiz and score card etc.

# APP FOR CERAMIC TILE AND STONE INDUSTRY- (NOV. 22 - DEC 2023)

- Managing 4 member under me as frontend Tech Lead in largest industrial research organization.
- Taking decisions on distributing the work in team and in sync with backend and devops team to work fast.
- Worked on improving the frontend arch. and made the app responsive for iPad users.
- I review the code, testing on iPad and desktop before merging.
- Discussion with UX team to design the responsive UI and flexible by taking specs for reusable components.
- Been Good in communication with the Business team resulting in taking smooth Inception to delivery of the product on time.
- Using IBM Cloud for deployment and doing sandbox testing